M-mom?
Are you awake?
Mom?
Zoso. what are you doing up?
It's still early.
Go back to sleep.
I Can't. Olive is scared.
Mom?
Down here.
Zoso. what are you doing
under here?
Mom. I told you...
I don't like
that stupid baby name anymore.
My name's Zoe.
And I'm under here
because I'm hiding.
Olive said we had to hide.
She dreamed they found us.
Who did?
The breathers.
Hey. What did
we just talk about?
Our new rule. remember?
Rule number four.
We're not allowed
to talk about them anymore.
I didn't. Olive did.
Well. you can tell olive
that no one found us.
Dad's been keeping watch
all night. just like always.
We're safe here.
You hear that. olive?
My smile is stuck.
Her smile's stuck.
That means she doesn't
want to be smiling anymore.
That means she's still scared.
Would it make olive feel better
if we went
and checked with dad?
It's okay.
All right.
Come on.
It's okay.
Mom. look.
That's just dad.
It doesn't look like dad.
Uh-oh. someone had
another nightmare. huh?
Oh. d-dad.
Hey. hey.
I thought we told those
silly nightmares to go away.
We did.
Well. then
why are you so scared?
Better ask olive about that.
Oh. was it olive
this time. huh?
How does she even sleep
with her eyes open all the time?
Dad. don't be mean.
I'm just wondering.
She wants a report.
Well. then I better
consult my notes.
Hmm.
My glasses. please.
Thank you.
So...
My watch started at 10:00.
At. uh. 2:00. I played
seven games of solitaire.
Won four. lost three.
Lost four. won three.
Miss Zoe.
you see right through me.
At 5:00. a couple of deer
ran overhead.
And at 6:00 in the morning.
I heard little footsteps.
Possibly belonging
to my rascal of a daughter!
Hmm?
But other than that. nothing.
Not a creature was stirring.
not even a...
A breather?
Zoso.
No.
Not even a... you know.
And the locks?
They still hold fast?
Do you wanna check?
Can I? No.
Ray. I told you I don't want her
going up there anymore.
What? This little monkey?
She can handle it.
Yeah. I can handle it. mom.
I know the rules.
One. never be loud.
I know you know the rules.
Two. never lose control.
Three. never open the door.
Four. never talk
about the breathers.
Careful. Zoso. your shoe.
Got it. mom.
Hold fast?
Hold fast.
Can't I just go barefoot?
No. that wouldn't be right.
Why not?
Because We're not animals. Zoe.
I need you to remember that.
But it's not like
I'm going outside or anything.
Well. who needs to go outside
when we brought the sun with us?
Another beautiful day. huh?
Mm-hmm.
Do you wanna make it official?
Not too hard. okay? I don't want
you to slip and cut your hand.
I got it. mom.
Okay.
How many days is that now?
Well. if you don't remember.
just count them.
They're lined up in rows of 25.
and there are how many rows?
One. two. three. eight. nine...
12.
So 25 times 12 makes?
300 plus the one
just I marked. so 301.
That's it.
See? Those math lessons
are really paying off.
Give me a kiss.
That means she's hungry.
Let's see here.
We've got hominy...
Corn...
Potatoes...
Beans...
And peaches...
Peaches. Definitely peaches.
You know.
we had peaches yesterday.
We can have them again
tomorrow.
But I was thinking today.
maybe we should try something
with a little protein.
Maybe beans. for once.
Ew. beans are the worst.
Dad? Yeah?
Beans or peaches?
Uh. I don't know.
Peaches.
Peaches sound
pretty good to me.
Ray.
Uh. how about we take a vote?
All those in favor of beans.
please raise your hand.
One vote for beans.
Now. all those in favor
of deliciously sweet
and juicy peaches.
please raise your hand.
Sorry. hon.
Two against one.
Three.
Is Darlene acting up again?
Oh. she's a tough gal.
She just needs a little
encouragement. that's all.
Hm.
There we go.
Told you she was tough.
Mom. dad! The peaches are gone!
Not funny. Zoso.
I'm serious!
Someone stole them!
God. that's 12. That's 12 cans.
That's almost
two weeks of rations.
There are no more peaches?
Uh. no. No more peaches.
Something must've been
drawn to the sugar.
Something with teeth.
What has teeth like that?
A rat. probably.
But a rat couldn't get in here.
I checked the door.
it's hold fast.
The door is not
the only way in.
Can the breathers
get in there too?
Zoso.
Can they?
No. they're too big
to fit in there.
But a rat could.
If it's a rat.
it's still in here somewhere.
We have to keep an eye out.
We have to find it
before it steals any more food.
In the meantime. we'll have to
cut down on our rations.
Dad. they're already so small.
I'm sorry. Zoe.
I really am.
I'm not gonna
ask you again. Eat.
Mom. I told you
I don't want stupid beans.
Hey. Zoso.
remember rule number two.
Never lose control.
Never let anger take over.
Rule number five.
never call me Zoso.
I just wanted some peaches.
Well. a thief stole them.
and now We're all gonna
have to give some things up.
I already have nothing.
I'm stuck in here.
I Can't even go outside.
I don't have any friends...
Except olive. and she can
only say five things.
What about us? What?
Well. you said
you don't have any friends.
What about us?
Mom and I aren't your friends?
You know what I mean.
No. actually. I don't.
I think it's real silly
to say you don't have anything
when you really have
everything.
Yeah. right. Yeah. right.
Look at that.
How many days
did you say that was?
301.
Now. we shouldn't
have been around
for any one of those days.
but just when we needed it.
we found this shelter.
And it's given us
food. a home. a life.
And for all we know.
we could be the only ones left.
the only ones still alive.
So every one of those marks
is really a miracle.
A miracle?
That's right. A miracle.
And this food is gonna allow you
to live another day.
And that means another hatch
can be drawn. right?
Yeah. I guess so.
So you see. those nasty. cold.
mushy beans on your plate.
they're really
their own kind of miracle too.
And if you eat
your mushy miracles for us...
Then maybe we can
take a trip afterwards.
A trip? Really?
Really.
But you better eat fast.
'cause I finished my miracle
beans. and I want more!
Careful with it. dad.
That goes there.
Joey's house goes there.
All right. Off we go.
Eight.
Five. six. seven...
Sylvia's ice cream!
Okay.
Let me get the door.
Door's open.
The chimes ring above you.
And look. There's Sylvia
standing behind the counter.
and she's wearing
that silly cone-shaped apron.
"Good morning. little Zoe."
And she hands you one of those
little. pink plastic spoons.
Then you run your other hand
along that cold
glass countertop.
Inside. you see
barrels and barrels
of Sylvia's
fresh homemade ice cream.
Now. it's still early. so she's
got all the best flavors.
Salted honey.
peanut butter brittle crunch.
and. of course. your favorite.
Strawberry shortcake.
Are you there?
You happy now?
Till tomorrow.
Uh. you win.
I win.
Aha! I win.
Everything's gonna work out.
I'm trying to believe that. ray.
I really am.
But imaginary ice cream
isn't gonna feed our daughter.
I'm just trying
to keep her spirits up.
And you are.
But what happens
when she gets sick?
We've lost a lot of weight
already. all of us.
And now...
And now We're just gonna have to
find a way to get more food.
Real food.
Go to the damn surface
if I have to.
You Can't. ray. They're...
They're still looking for us.
Yeah. well. I can fight them.
That's suicide.
and you know it.
You remember our promise
when we first got here?
Zoe comes first.
No matter the cost.
The important thing is
we still haven't been found.
Except by a rat.
But only by a rat.
Oh. honey.
Try changing
your point of view.
This shelter can be a prison.
or it can be a home.
Beans can be beans.
or they can be...
Miracle beans.
Why not?
Because I'm not
nine years old. ray.
I get what You're
trying to do for Zoso.
But I don't believe
in miracles.
Not anymore.
You should.
This is our life now.
and we have to live it
the best we can.
Or else what's the point?
The point is to stay alive.
We can do that...
And still live.
Hmm?
Ray?
Huh?
What are you doing?
Living.
We got to be real quiet.
Relax.
I'll see you tonight.
Have fun.
Come on. come on. come on! No.
no. no! Too far to walk there!
Mom! Mom! Please!
Zoe!
Mom! Dad! They're coming!
Uh-oh. That's a doozy.
A five and a two.
So. five divided by two is...
Two and a half.
Bingo.
You can move your car now.
Come on. I thought this would be
a fun change of pace.
It's still boring math. mom.
Even with Kingsville.
Well. if it's so boring.
how come olive's still smiling?
That's her fake smile.
That's why she looks
a little. you know...
Creepy?
I didn't mean that. honey.
She just... needs a bath.
That's all.
How about we have
another go around the board
and then we take a break. okay?
Okay.
Mom. do you think dad's right?
Right about what?
You know. about the three of us
being the only ones left.
The periscope?
That's right.
What do you want me
to do with it?
What do you think?
I want you to look up there.
On the surface?
Mm-hmm.
I thought you said
I wasn't allowed to do that.
ever. ever. ever.
or I'd be dead meat.
Yeah. well...
I'm trying something new today.
What?
Relaxing.
So. what do you see?
Nothing.
The school. Playground.
Dad's right.
It's just us left.
Us and olive.
But do you see us and olive?
No. mom.
Do you even see
the shelter door?
I Can't see the door.
It's covered.
Exactly.
When we first came down here.
dad and I made sure
to hide the door. remember?
So that no one
could ever find us.
So?
So... sometimes...
Just because
you Can't see something
doesn't mean it's not there.
Sometimes
the truth's hidden from us.
So you think our friends
could really be out there?
They're just hidden like us?
They could. They'd have to be.
Because the breathers
would be hunting them too.
Zoso.
Yeah. that's right. Because the
breathers would be hunting them too.
They hate us a lot. don't they?
To keep hunting us like that?
I don't know that it's hate.
It's just...
They're different than we are.
and that makes them as scared
of us as we are of them.
Because of what happened
that day?
Yeah. because of
what happened that day.
You said "breathers."
Yeah.
The thief.
He's back.
Don't look.
Hey.
What's wrong?
It's the thief.
That son of a bitch.
I'll kill it. Just stay back
in case it makes a run for it.
No. no. you stay back.
I'll kill it.
No. I'll kill it.
We Can't all kill it. guys.
You remember that thanksgiving
at aunt Cathy's
a couple years ago.
with that insane possum
in the backyard?
Who took care of that thing?
After dad kills it.
can we eat it for dinner?
Zoso. quiet.
Get it. dad!
Dad!
Getting away. dad! Hurry!
I know!
Dad!
Mom!
Wow.
That was awesome.
Even more awesome than
when dad killed the possum?
Definitely.
What is that?
Get back. Get back there.
Aah! God damn it!
Turn it... turn it off. dad.
It's gonna break. Get back.
Get back!
Back!
It's burning Kingsville!
We'll put it out!
Just stay here!
Stay here!
No. not again.
Ray! Help me!
Don't break her!
Darlene can take it!
Ray. come on!
I told you she's tough!
All right. get back. get back!
Zoso! I told you to stay back!
I Can't see a damn thing.
Hold on.
Where's Zoso?
Zoe? Zoso?
Zoso?
Zoso.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Did the fire burn you?
I'm just scared.
Well. There's nothing
to be scared of anymore.
We put the fire out.
Nobody's hurt.
Look.
Even olive's okay.
Just a little dirty.
that's all.
See?
Everything's gonna be okay.
No. dad.
It's not.
It's not gonna be okay.
They're gonna see.
Who?
The breathers.
My God.
Mmm! Hello. bacon.
Where'd your little sous-chef
run off to?
Upstairs. getting ready.
Still?
How long does it take
to put on a swimsuit?
Long time when You're trying
to impress Joey.
Joey? Yeah. he's coming
to the "y" with us.
Joey Neary next door?
He's a real cutie.
don't you think?
I think he can barely
tie his own shoes.
That's what I think.
Joey Neary.
Come on. you remember
young love. don't you?
Yeah. well. I had definitely
outgrown nerf weapons
by our first date.
I don't like this at all.
Dad. why didn't you tell me?
What? Tell you what?
That Joey's going on vacation.
We were supposed to play
Marco polo.
Well. that Can't be true. because
I talked to Jillian last night.
Just leave it. We don't need it.
Come on. We have to.
Come on. come on.
Leave everything there.
We got what we need.
Come on.
Hey. Ted?
That's good.
Jillian?
What else?
Ted? Is everything okay?
Jillian?
Hey. Joey. What's going on?
I don't want to leave.
Why do you have to leave?
The government man.
He said... the virus.
It changes people bad.
The what? What kind of virus?
Joey. come on.
We have to go.
Jillian. where are you going? I'm
sorry. Claire. There's no time.
What's happening? Just get Zoe and get
as far away from Kingsville as you can.
Get in the car. Let's go.
Tell Zoe I'm sorry
I Can't play Marco polo!
Ted!
Can't go back for the others.
Where's everyone going?
Come on. Sandra. Just
pack that up! I'll do my best!
The breathers.
They're gonna see it.
aren't they?
Aren't they?
Well. it's sundown.
Maybe it's too dark
to see the smoke.
Maybe.
Can you see any smoke?
Don't forget rule two. Claire.
We have to stay calm. No matter what.
we have to stay under control.
We have to think.
Anyone within a mile of here
will have seen that smoke.
The breathers are gonna
come for us. I know it.
Zoe. let mom and I talk
for a minute. okay?
But they're gonna find us.
just like olive dreamed.
They're not gonna find us.
They might.
Claire. stop.
Stop it? Stop what?
I'm just trying to figure out
what the hell to do here. ray.
We're not gonna do anything.
Even if they see the smoke...
And I don't think they will...
By the time they get here.
it'll be gone.
They'll have no idea
where it came from.
It won't matter...
They'll know We're here.
and they'll search the area
for us.
So let them come.
They've searched here
a dozen times before.
They've never found us.
And they're not
gonna find us now.
Dad's right.
We're still hidden.
I checked. remember?
All agreed We're safe.
please raise your hand.
Two against one.
Three.
What's wrong. mom?
The wood's burned.
So?
So burned wood makes ash.
We're not hidden anymore...
Are we?
Oh. I don't think
they'll notice.
Do you really
want to take that risk?
We don't have another choice.
We cover the ash.
How?
We'd have to go
onto the surface.
But what about the third rule?
Never. ever open the door.
Sometimes rules...
Even mom rules...
Have to be broken.
Listen to me.
If you hear anything up there.
anything but me and dad.
I want you
to lock the door behind us.
What? No. I'm going up there
with you. I'm gonna help.
Out of the question. Zoso.
It's "Zoe."
Stop treating me like a baby.
I'm protecting you.
But what if
you need me to protect you?
I can fight if I have to.
No. you Can't.
My rules still apply to you.
So no matter what happens
up there.
no matter what you hear.
do not open the door.
But...
I need you to promise me that.
Promise.
We'll have to move fast.
I don't wanna be out there
for more than three minutes.
Three minutes.
Okay.
They're going this way. olive.
Come on.
No. I don't know
where they went.
It's just them. olive.
They're okay.
Mom! Dad!
Look out behind you!
Hurry!
Dad!
Mom! Dad!
Mom!
Dad!
What the hell are you doing?
I told you to stay inside.
Slow down.
We Can't understand you.
Breathers!
Look out!
It's just deer. Zoe.
Nothing to be scared of.
Just Bambi.
They looked scared.
Aw. don't be silly.
She's right. ray.
They're running away.
Running away from something.
We have to
get back in the shelter.
Careful.
What happened?
Did you see something?
Be quiet! Quiet.
What is it. dad?
Footsteps.
I think it's just one.
Why? Why just one?
They've always traveled
in groups before.
I don't know.
Maybe he's the only one
who saw the smoke.
He's headed this way.
Zoso. we have to stay quiet.
Rule number one. remember?
Never be loud.
I know. I-I'm trying.
Try harder.
If he hears us.
he will find us.
Do you understand me?
Zoe. Zoe. Zoe.
Zoe. come here.
Have a seat.
What do you say
we get out of here?
'Cause look what I found.
With this car...
You can go anywhere you want.
Anywhere in the world.
Any time.
Where do you want to go?
My bed. Yeah?
My old bed.
Yeah.
That's an excellent choice.
Okay. Okay.
Ka-plop.
You collapse on your bed...
Exhausted after a long day.
And you pull
those warm pink polka dot sheets
all the way up to your eyes.
You hug
all your stuffed animals.
Puffy bear. duck duck.
Cathypillar.
Kissing them good night.
You can feel the fan
on your nightstand
blowing a soft breeze
through your hair.
And then you look up
at the ceiling above you.
where we hung
those glow-in-the-dark stars...
And they shine for you.
So There's always light...
Even when you sleep.
Even when you dream.
Are you there?
Yeah.
I'm there.
Can you see the stars?
Mm.
Let it go. let it go.
My smile is stuck.
Stuck. Stuck. Stuck. Stuck.
Stuck. Stuck.
Stuck.
Stuck. Stuck. Stuck. Stuck.
No.
Please. Please fit in.
He Can't get in here. can he?
Hold fast. right. dad?
He's too strong!
We need something
to brace the door!
Something tough.
Go! Go!
Mom. you Can't go up there!
Just tell dad to hurry!
Dad! Hurry!
I am hurrying!
Unh!
Mom. are you okay?!
I'm okay! Just stay down there!
Dad. hurry!
God!
Ray!
He's almost through!
Hold on!
Dad!
Watch out!
Ray. give me the pipe!
Wedge it under the handle!
Watch out. mom!
Watch out. Claire!
Die!
Ray!
Ray! Ray! He's not getting in!
He's not getting in!
It'll hold!
It will.
Okay?
Okay.
Hey.
Hold fast?
Hold fast.
He's still up there.
Why isn't he leaving?
Why won't he just go away?
I don't know.
He's up to something.
What could he be up to?
Why is he still standing there?
That's what he's doing.
He's waiting.
Waiting for what?
The rest of them.
Hey. look. Zoe. there it is.
The water tower over there...
You see it?
So once We're past that.
We're out of Kingsville.
Then we'll be safe?
Safe from the sick people?
That's right. sweetie.
Safe from the sick people.
Why are all those people
headed back?
I don't know.
I thought you said
we couldn't stay.
that it was dangerous.
Maybe everything's okay now.
You think that's possible?
I don't know.
Got to be able
to get something here.
Maybe A.M.?
Ray. watch out!
Let us out!
There's nowhere else to go!
All civilians in Kingsville.
Must return to their homes
at once.
Until the CDC
stabilizes the outbreak.
This is a quarantine order
signed by governor schroeder.
Under emergency code 11.
This is for your own safety.
Repeat...
All civilians in Kingsville.
Must return to their homes
at once.
Until the CDC
stabilizes the outbreak.
This is a quarantine order
signed by governor schroeder.
Under emergency code 11.
This is for your own safety.
All civilians in Kingsville.
Must return to their homes
at once.
Until the CDC
stabilizes the outbreak.
Mom. what's a "core and tine"?
Quarantine.
It means
they're not letting us out.
You mean We're trapped in here?
The CDC is working closely
with the national guard.
To support the deployment...
You will receive
further notification.
Of the response teams...
Get back!
Mom. Dad.
They're here.
Darlene's not gonna hold!
We need something else!
Go!
Run!
Get Zoe to the bedroom!
Go! Hold on!
That's not gonna last long.
Ray. help me!
How long is that gonna last?!
Couple of minutes.
We've got to get out of here!
They're blocking the door!
Mom. dad.
The door's
not the only way out.
The periscope!
I think we can fit. I don't
know about you. ray.
I'll be fine. Just...
Hurry.
Dad! Claire!
Okay. ray. It's clear.
Get Zoso.
You ready? Get Zoso!
Come on.
Ray. now!
Here. watch your head.
Take your mom's hand! No!
You got her? Got her!
Okay. ray. she's up. Come on.
I Can't fit.
Oh. come on!
Claire. grab my wrist!
What? Grab it!
Hold tight.
Oh. God! Dad!
Dad! Dad!
Aah! God!
Are you okay?!
I'm o...
I'm okay.
No. daddy! Come on!
Ray!
Remember our promise.
Zoe comes first.
Aah!
Come on.
Come on!
No! Ray!
No. daddy! Oh. ray!
Oh. God. help!
Daddy! Daddy!
Ohh! God!
Daddy!
No! No! Dad! Let me go!
We can help him!
I promised him that I would
protect you! No! No!
I promised him that I would protect you!
I don't care!
I promised him!
I hate you!
It's okay. It's okay. I just
...I just... let me go.
It's okay.
We have to run.
Run!
Olive! Olive!
Zoso! Come back!
Run!
Are you okay. honey?
Yeah. I'm okay.
Come on.
Where... where are we?
Where it all started.
What do we do?!
Run! Keep running!
The breathers! They're coming!
She dreamed they found us.
They're still looking for us.
They hate us a lot. don't they?
To keep hunting us like that.
They've always
traveled in groups before.
Yeah. well. I can fight them.
That's suicide.
and you know it.
What's a "core and tine"?
It means
they're not letting us out.
The breathers.
Let us go!
Let us go! Let us out!
No!
Mom. it's an earthquake.
No. sweetie. it Can't be.
Kingsville
doesn't have earthquakes.
Why the hell
does the CDC need military jets?
They're turning around.
They just told everyone
to go back into town.
Mom. dad. they're coming!
Come on!
We got to get out of here!
Come on. come on. come on!
No. no. no!
Too far to walk there!
Kingsville elementary! What?!
There's a fallout shelter
out back!
But I don't know if it's safe.
Well. it's safer than here.
Come on.
Come on!
Got to go. guys. Go.
Where is it? There!
Where's the door?! There!
- They're coming! Hurry!
- Ray. hurry!
Let's go. Come on. I got you.
All right. come on! Come on!
Claire! Shut it now!
Are you okay?
Claire. are you okay?
Yeah. I'm okay.
Are you guys?
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. We're...
We're okay.
Ohh.
Oh. they have everything here.
Look at all this food.
Hey. Zoe.
Look at all this.
Huh?
There's...
There's books and games and...
Hey. dad?
More toys. that...
Ye... yeah?
How long
do we have to stay here?
I... I don't know.
Not... hopefully not very long.
W-we just got to wait
till they clear this up.
And then...
Honey. w...
What happened up there
was a mistake.
It's a terrible.
t-terrible mistake.
It wasn't a mistake.
The shelter door cut me.
The virus
must have gone airborne.
We're infected.
Please. just let us go.
No! Just let us go.
You cooperate.
answer my questions.
I'll do what I can
to help you and your daughter.
Do you understand?
Yes. yes.
That shelter we found you in.
How long have you been there?
Since the beginning.
Did you ever come into contact
with anyone else?
Family? Neighbors?
It was only us.
Dad says
We're the only ones left.
"Zoe."
I have a little girl
about your age.
Goddamn shame.
No!
What are you doing?
You said you would help us.
On my order. I won't
let you touch her.
I won't let you touch her!
I will not let you touch her!
Mom. never lose control!
Keep away! It's too dangerous!
Keep away. keep away.
keep away!
Remember rule number two...
Never lose control.
Keep away.
Don't forget rule two. Claire.
No matter what.
we have to stay under control.
We have to stay calm.
Never let anger take over.
No. no. no!
They're different than we are.
and that makes them
as scared of us
as we are of them.
We're not animals.
Sometimes
the truth's hidden from us.
Daddy! Let me go! Help!
Come on!
Take him out!
All stations. this is echo one.
Target secure. Target secure.
How many casualties?
Four casualties.
Two targets contained.
Gunship. qrf out of bounds.
Miles out. Stand by.
Support is on the way.
Run! Mommy!
Stop!
You don't have to kill him.
It's okay.
We're sa...
Aah!
Remember rule number two. Zoso?
Remember rule number two.
You can stop it.
You can stop it. Zoso.
Zoe. That's it.
Come back to me.
Zoe.
That's it. that's it.
Hey.
Mom.
Yeah. It's me.
You saved me. Protected me.
I know.
You called me "Zoe." I know.
Come here.
Hey. come on.
We got to go.
Careful.
You're hurt.
Here.
Thank you.
What do we do with him?
We let him live.
Mom.
Look.
Daddy!
Daddy.
I love you.
I'm not leaving you.
And if...
I know I'm not going far.
You can always visit me. Hm?
Yeah.
J-j-just t-take a tri... trip.
Ohh.
Dad?
Are you there?
No. daddy!
No! No!
We Can't stay here. sweetie.
We have to go.
Where?
We have to hide.
Mom? Mom?
Are you awake?
Zoe.
What are you doing up already?
Go back to sleep.
I Can't.
Olive is scared.
What is it?
What's wrong with olive?
We heard something.
I think a breather's coming.
No. sweetie. You just had
another nightmare.
Quick. hide down.
Marco!
Polo?
Joey Neary?
I found you.
Who's down there?
Joey. where've you been?
My God.
Ted.
Wait. Oh. come on.
No. it's okay.
Are they all different like us?
Yeah. But it's normal here.
Come on.
Do you see it?
See what?
The sun.
That means it's 302 now.
302 days.
Not days.